Guide to the New York Foundation For the Arts (NYFA) Records MSS.515
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII. Fiscal Sponsorship, 1971-2011; 52 linear feet in 52 record cartons
  - Subseries C. Artists' Projects, 1982-2011; 36 linear feet in 36 record cartons
    - Bank, Mirra, 1998-2000 (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Bank, Mirra, 2000-2007 (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - Baratloo, Mojden, 1988-1993 (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Baratloo, Mojden, 1989-1992 (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Barbata, Laura, 2003-2009 (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Belle, Anne, 1992-1997 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Belle, Anne, 1992-1997 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Beller, Hava Kohar, 1988-1994 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Beller, Hava Kohar, 1988-1994 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Beller, Hava Kohar, 1988-1994 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Beller, Hava Kohar, 1988-1994 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Ben-Shitrit, Orit, 2001-2004 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Bender, Gretchen, 1997-1998 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Bender, Jacob, 2002-2008 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Berlinger, Joseph, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Bergman, Penny, 1997-2005 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Berman, Jonathan, 1989-1993 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Berman, Jonathan, 1994-2003 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Berman, Jonathan, 1994-2004 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Berman, John, 2002-2007 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Berman, Jonathan, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Bermel, Derek, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Bernberg, Lana, 1998-2004 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Bernstein, Sue Renée, 2000-2001 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Bernstein, Sue Renée, 1998-2000 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - Berry, Glynis, 1999-2005 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - Bery, Niki, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - Beyer, Britt, 1998-2005 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - Bosmajian, Vilka, 1999-2004 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - Boston, Michon, 2001-2004 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Botti, Susan, 1996-1997 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Bouiss, Elizabeth, 2001-2008 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Bowes, Ed, 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Bowes, Ed, 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Barcimanto, Victor, 1995-1998 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Baren, Joan, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Barkan, Stanley, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Barkan, Stanley, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Barr, Burt, 1985-1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Barr, Burt, 1987-1989 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Barr, Burt, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Barr, Burt, 1989-1992 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Barry, Judith, 2005-2010 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Battenfield, Jackie, 2007-2009 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Battles, Wendy, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Bauman, Suzanne, 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Baki, Kadambari, 1998-2004 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Beall, Aaron, 1997 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Beall, Aaron, 1998-2001 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Bear, Liza, 1988-1998 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Beatty, Maria, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Beatty, Maria, 1989-1992 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Beaumont, Betty, 2002-2006 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Beaumont, Betty, 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Beckley, Connie, 1999-2006 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Bell, Martin/Walker, Lou Ann, 1993 (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Belle, Anne, 1983-1991 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Belle, Anne, 1983-1991 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Belle, Anne, 1990-2001 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Bialor, Perry, 1993-1994 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Bieulawa, Lisa, 2002-2005 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Bishop, Helen, 1983-1989 (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Bishop, Helen, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Black, Wade, 1985-1987 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Black, Wade, 1987-1990 (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Blackwood, Christian, 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1984-1985 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1985-1987 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1986-1988 (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1986-1989 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1988-1995 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1991-1996 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1998 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 1998-1999 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Blackwood, Christian, 1990-1993 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Bieulawa, Lisa, 1995-1997 (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Bowes, Ed, 1991-1992 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Brancaccio, Ralph, 1994-1999 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Brancaccio, Ralph, 1994-1999 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1988-2007 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1988-2007 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1988-2007 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1988-2007 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1988-2007 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1988-2007 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1988-2007 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 2003-2004 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 2003-2007 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 2005-2007 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 2005-2007 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Bai, Marilyn, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Braverman, Barry, 1991-1995 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Bowes, Ed, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Cabezas, Maria, 1999-2002 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - Cacheiro, Jorge Luis, 1996-1999 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - Cajori, Charles, 1991-1993 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Camarda, George, 1996-2000 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Cammisa, Rebecca, 1999-2004 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Cammisa, Rebecca, 2003-2005 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Cantow, Roberta, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Camissa, Rebecca, 1999 (Box 50, Folder 27)
    - Cantow, Roberta, 1987-1990 (Box 50, Folder 28)
    - Cantow, Roberta, 1988-1991 (Box 50, Folder 29)
    - Cantow, Roberta, 1991-1994 (Box 50, Folder 30)
    - Caplan, Elliot, 2004-2006 (Box 50, Folder 31)
    - Brandt, Yanna Kroyt, 2001-2002 (Box 50, Folder 32)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 2002-2004 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Blackwood, Michael, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Block, Doug, 1996-1999 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Block, Tom, 2003-2006 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Bloodworth, Sandra, 2005-2006 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Bloomgarden, John, 1992-1995 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Bluds, Serge, 1998-2004 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Blumenfeld, Barry, 1999-2002 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Blumenfeld, Barry, 2000-2004 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Blumenfeld, Barry, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Boebel, Chris, 2002-2005 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Boehm, Frank, 1983-1984 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Bogart, Beth, 2010 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Bokelberg, Oliver, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Boker, Akiva, 2000-2004 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Book, Lynn, 1996-1997 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Borten, Helen, 1998 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Borten, Helen, 2001-2004 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Borten, Helen, 2005 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Borten, Helen, 2006-2008 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Borzova, Alla, 2000-2005 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Breitbart, Eric, 1989-1992 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Bretherton, Monica, 1998-1999 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Bridges, Lester, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Brigham, Joan/Janney, Christopher, 1989-1994 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Brigham, Joan, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Bright, Nancee Oku, 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Bright, Nancee Oku, 1999-2000 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Bright, Nancee Oku, 2001-2003 (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Brisco, Carla/Ornitz, Alexandra, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Brodsky, Phyllis, 2002-2007 (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Brodsky, Phyllis, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Brockway, JoAnne, 2004-2008 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Bronte, Lydia, 1992-1993 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Brooks, Terri, 2001-2010 (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Broughel, Barbara, 1996-1998 (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Broughel, Barbara, 2002-2006 (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Brown, Jim, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Brown, Jim, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Brown, Jim, 1998-2005 (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Cardona, Wally, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Carey, Catherine, 1999-2000 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Carlson, Ann, 1997-2001 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Carlson, Ann, 1997-2004 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Carlson, Ann, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Carlson, Ann, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Carmel, Kate, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Carpenter, Jeff, 1998-2010 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Carpenter, Sheri, 1999-2005 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Carroll, Mary Ellen, 2002-2005 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Carter, Gilles/Smith, David, 2001-2004 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Carter, Gilles/Smith, David, 2001-2004 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Carter, Gilles, 2004-2005 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Carter, Kabir, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Carty, Laurence, 1989-1990 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Carvalho, Denise, 1999-2002 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Carvalho, Denise, 2000-2002 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Carvalho, Josely, 2000-2005 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Cantania, John, 2003-2005 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Carpenter, Shari L., 1999 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Carvalho, Denise, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Carvalho, Denise, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Catanach, Daniel, 2001-2004 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Catania, John, 2000-2009 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Cecere, Jennifer, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Cerf, Charlotte, 1998-2004 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Cerf, Charlotte, 1998-2004 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Crafts, Lisa, 2002-2004 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Cramer, Erin, 1989-1994 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Cramer, James, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 30)
    - Creighton, Virginia, 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 31)
    - Creighton, Virginia, 2010 (Box 52, Folder 32)
    - Cross, Kara, 2000-2004 (Box 52, Folder 33)
    - Cryer, Mark, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 34)
    - Cudlipp, Chandler, 1988-1989 (Box 52, Folder 35)
    - Cummings, Conrad, 1986-1999 (Box 52, Folder 36)
    - Cunningham, Kevin, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 37)
    - Cuneo, Maryann, 1999 (Box 52, Folder 38)
    - Curran, Sean, 1999-2001 (Box 52, Folder 39)
    - Currie, Russell, 1998-2004 (Box 52, Folder 40)
    - Currie, Russell, 1998-2004 (Box 52, Folder 41)
    - Currier, Nathan, 2003-2004 (Box 52, Folder 42)
    - Carr, Benita, 2007 (Box 52, Folder 43)
    - Brown, Jim, 1998-2005 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Bigbee, Victoria, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Burch, Eva, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Burns, Donna Lynn, 1995-2004 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Burroughs, Jim/Baumanm Suzanne, 1985-1986 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Burroughs, Jim, 1988-1991 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Butterworth, Dan, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Bylander, Sheri, 2004-2005 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Byron, Toby, 1993-1994 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Chamecki, Rosane, 2000-2002 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Chang, Barbara/Soon Min, Yong, 1987-1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Cheng, Anita, 2003-2004 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Cheng, Joanne, 2002-2004 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Child, Abigail, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Child, Abigail, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Child, Abigail, 1994-1995 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Chimerine, Lawrence, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Christopher, Mark, 1998-1999 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Claire, Andrea, 1998-2002 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Clarke, Kevin, 1990-1992 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Clarke, Shannon, 2001-2005 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Clem, Robert, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Cloutier, Jack Macintosh, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Clem, Rovert, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Cohen, Duffie, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Cohen, Jem, 1989-1995 (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Cohen, Jem, 2003-2005 (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Cohen, John, 1988-1991 (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Cohen, John, 1991-1994 (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Cohen, John, 1993-1995 (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Cohen, Maki, 2003-2007 (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Coigney, Martha W., 1988-1993 (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Coleman, Grisha, 2002-2003 (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Coleman, Jim, 1998-2004 (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Conde, Sidiki, 2001-2004 (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Conde, Sidiki, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Conley, Brian, 1995-2005 (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Cook, Mariana, 2007-2008 (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Corbin, Gary, 1998-2006 (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Currier, Nathan, 2003-2008 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Curtis, Tonya Denise, 1999-2002 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - D'Auria, Mark, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Dabell, Frank, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Daniels, Mark, 1988-1991 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Daniels, Mark, 1988-1993 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Danilian, Sergei, 2000-2002 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Daum, Menachem, 1992-2002 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Daum, Menachem, 2003-2005 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Davidson, Selina Lewis, 2006-2007 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Davis, John R., 1992-1993 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Davis, Peter, 1987-1989 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Davis, Peter, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Dawson, Barbara, 2001-2007 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - deCamp, Kyle, 1997-2002 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - deCamp, Kyle, 2004-2008 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - De Domonicis, Joseph, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - DeDawney, Marilys Belt, 1999-2003 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - De Luca, Maria, 1982-1991 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - De Luca, Maria, 1982-1991 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Dean, Jose, 1985-1993 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Daen, Josie, 1985-1998 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Decter, Joshua, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Decter, Joshua, 1993-1994 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Delk, John, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Dello Joio, Justin, 1999-2011 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Dello Joio, Justin, 2005 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Delson, Susan, 1995 (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Demay, Layla, 2001-2003 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Dennis, Donna, 2002-2009 (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Des Lauriers, Stefan, 1996-2005 (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Dzesjardins, Rosemary, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Deussing, Ryan, 1999-2001 (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - DiJiacomo, Michael, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Dickson, Deborah, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Ding, Lopni, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Dintenfass, Terry, 1993 (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Disposti, John, 1997-2004 (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - DoBrooks, Lotus, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Donello, Jennifer, 2007 (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Donovan, William, 1989-1998 (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Dorman, Joe, 1999-2002 (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - Dorman, Joe, 1999-2002 (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Corbin, Patrick, 2006 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Corn, Kahane, 1991-1992 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Cornyn, Alison, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Cornyn, Alison, 2002-2004 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Cornyn, Allison, 2002-2005 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Corrigan, John, 1983-1995 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Coston, Peter, 2001-2009 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Cox, Leonard, 2001-2005 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Averbach, Rhoda, 1998-2000 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Averbach, Rhoda, 1998-2000 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Averbach, Rhoda, 2001-2003 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Avila, Homer/Weeks, Edisa, 1996-2002 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Avila, Jac, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Axinn, Audrey, 2007-2009 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Aylon, Helene, 1995-1999 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Aytom, William, 1998-2005 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Ayton-Shenker, Diana, 2003-2005 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - B, Beth, 1987-1991 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - B, Beth, 1988-1990 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - B, Beth, 1988-1991 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - B, Beth, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - B, Beth, 1990-1993 (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - B, Beth, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - B, Beth, 1991-1994 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - B, Beth, 1992-1995 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - B, Beth, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - B, Beth, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - B, Beth, 1996-1999 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - B, Beth, 1998-2002 (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - B, Beth, 1998-2002 (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - B, Beth, 1999-2002 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - B, Beth, 2000-2002 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Babcock, Richard, 2000-2004 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - Bady, Robin, 2000-2002 (Box 55, Folder 34)
    - Baer, Adam, 1994-2004 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Baer, Nancy, 1985-1991 (Box 55, Folder 36)
    - Baer, Suzie, 1989-1992 (Box 55, Folder 37)
    - Baer, Suzie, 1998-2005 (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - Bagley, Ben, 1988-2000 (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - Bagley, Ben, 1989-2004 (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - Balash, Muriel, 1984-1986 (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - Balash, Muriel, 1984-1999 (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - Balash, Muriel, 1984-1999 (Box 55, Folder 43)
    - Balash, Muriel, 1989 (Box 55, Folder 44)
    - Ball, Edward, 1994-1997 (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - Belle, Anne, 1992-1997 (Box 55, Folder 46)
    - Belle, Anne, 1992-1997 (Box 55, Folder 47)
    - Dorman, Joe, 1992-2002 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Dorman, Joseph, 2000-2004 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - DorVillier, DD, 2002-2005 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Dory, Elizabeth, 2001-2004 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Dowell, James/Kolamvakis, John, 1998-2001 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Dowell, James/Kolamvakis, John, 1998-2006 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Douglas, Brian, 2001-2004 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Douglas, Brian, 2001-2004 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Dressler, Shana, 1999-2004 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Drury, Andrew, 2003-2008 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Dufallo, Cornelius, 2006-2007 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Duffalo, Cornelius, 2007 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Dunlop, Bridgette, 2002-2007 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Dunn, Judy, 2009 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Dwass, Michael, 1994-2004 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Easdon, Josh, 1998-2004 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Ehrlich, Judd, 1997-2005 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Einfiger, Carmen, 2003-2006 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Eliopoulos, Christine, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Elliot, Stephen, 2003-2007 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Ellis, David, 1999-2004 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Ellis, Monica, 2000-2004 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Ellman, Liberty, 2004-2006 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Ellman, Liberty, 2006 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Ellsworth, Barry, 1990-1991 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Elson, Elizabeth, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Elson, Elizabeth, 2005 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Enwezor, Okwui, 1999-2001 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Erikson, Barbara, 1996-2000 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Erikson, Gordon, 1997-2000 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Eriksson, Alexander, 2002-2003 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Eriksson, Alexander, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Estrella, Olympia, 2002-2004 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - Eustace, David, 2007-2008 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Evans, Garth, 1990-2004 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Evans, Jenny, 1997-2002 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Everly, Bart, 2000-2005 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Fanshel, Susan, 1983-1987 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Fanshel, Susan, 1983-1987 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Fass, Robert, 2000-2008 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Fass, Robert, 2000-2008 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Faught, Margot, 1999-2002 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Fay, Leslie, 1991-1993 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Felder, David, 1999-2008 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Felder, David, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Feuerzeig, Jeff, 1991-1994 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Fishel, Deirdre, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Fisher, Jane, 2002-2005 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Fishman, Rachael, 2002-2002 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Fleischman, Stephanie, 1990-2004 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Fleischman, Stephanie, 1990-2004 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Fleischman, Stephanie, 2005-2008 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Fleming, Maureen, 1996-2006 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Fleming, Maureen, 1997-2006 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Fleming, Maureen, 1997-2006 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Fleming, Maureen, 1990 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Fleming, Maureen, 1997-2006 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Fleming, Maureen, 2001-2002 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Fletcher, Catherine, 2007-2009 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Flores, Gene, 1996 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Fockele, Jörg, 2003 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Fockele, Jörg, 2005-2008 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Fontes, Flavia, 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Forbes, Victor, 1991-1992 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Fox, Curtis, 1998-2001 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Fox, Jennifer, 1992-1998 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Fox, Jennifer, 1992-1998 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Franco, Danielle, 2006-2007 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Frasconi, Pablo, 1989-1994 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Fratkin, Leslie, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Freechman, Joel, 1981-1996 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Freedman, Joel, 1981-1996 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - Freedman, Joel, 1995-1996 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Freeman, Catherine, 1991-1995 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Freiburg, Conrad, 2005-2007 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Frelek, Ryszard, 1993-2000 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Freudenheim, Leslie, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Freund, Gerald, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Friedman, Peter, 1989-1994 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Friedman, Peter, 2000-2008 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Fries'Dat, Lulu, 2008 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Frost, Randy, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Fruchtman, Rob, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Fruchtman, Rob, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Galanis, Emmanuel, 1999-2005 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Galanis, Emmanuel, 1996-2005 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Gallagher, Stephen, 1989-1991 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Galvin, Jennifer, 2006-2008 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Gannon, Tim, 1994-1999 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Garcia, William, 1990-1993 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Gardner, Janet, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Gardner, Janet, 1999-2000 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Gardner, Janet, 2000-2003 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Gardner, Janet, 2002-2005 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Gardner, Janet, 2003-2009 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Gardner, Janet, 2003-2009 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Gardner, Janet, 2006-2007 (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - Gardner, Jeff, 1989-1993 (Box 58, Folder 26)
    - Gardner, Jeff, 1997-2009 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - Garrin, Paul, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - Garrin, Paul, 1989-1991 (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - Garrison, Maia Claire, 1999-2004 (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - Garrison, Matthew, 2000-2002 (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - Garrison, Matthew, 2003-2005 (Box 58, Folder 32)
    - Gashian, Gayana, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 33)
    - Gauthier, Douglas, 2000-2005 (Box 58, Folder 34)
    - George, Dan, 1983-1985 (Box 58, Folder 35)
    - Gerber, Carol Bennett, 1992-2000 (Box 58, Folder 36)
    - Giancoli, Mary Teresa, 2002-2006 (Box 58, Folder 37)
    - Gibson, Jodi, 2005-2006 (Box 58, Folder 38)
    - Gibson, Melissa James, 1997-2007 (Box 58, Folder 39)
    - Gibson, Melissa James, 1997-2007 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Giganti, Joanne, 1999-2004 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Gilchrist, Jane, 1991-1992 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Giganti, Joanne, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Gillespie, Chris, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Gladstone, Valerie, 2000-2001 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Glaser, Susan, 1998-2004 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Glaser, Susan, 1998-2005 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Glaser, Susan, 2005 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Glesta, Anita, 2003-2007 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Glick, Geoffrey, 1995-1997 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Glick, Geoffrey, 1996-2001 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Glück, Pearl, 1997-2004 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Glück, Pearl, 2004-2005 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Goede, Nina, 2000-2004 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Gold, Harry/Chiavetta, Carol, 1998-2002 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Gold, Harry/Chiavetta, Carol, 1998-2002 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Gold, Tom, 2001-2005 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Goldberg, Ilana, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Goldberg, RoseLee, 2001-2003 (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Goldhuber, Lawrence, 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Goldhuber, Lawrence, 2002-2004 (Box 59, Folder 22)